munsoft.com 2017-02-15

# MunSoft: Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the use of _MunSoft’s web site_.

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site. 

### Log Files

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

### Security

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore—as is the case with any organization—we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information. 

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us at [info@munsoft.com](mailto:info@munsoft.com).

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

### Contact Details

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us please e-mail us at [info@munsoft.com](mailto:info@munsoft.com).
